[Music]
how beautiful I want those red shoes
grandma please
okay how much
ten dollars
Thank you Grandma
[Music]
Karen what are you doing I'm dancing
grandma
[Music]
she is dancing here
she is dancing there
she is a good dancer that's right
[Music]
your grandma is in the hospital
Karen go home please sorry I can't
[Music]
oh I'm sleepy
oh Karen don't dance go to the hospital
now
foreign
thank you very much
I'm sorry Grandma
[Music]
[Applause]
mom where are you
I'm in the kitchen
what are you doing I'm making soup
can you help me
yes I can
don't run the soup is hot
where are you
I'm in the bedroom
[Music]
this is for you thank you
it's too hot
are you okay
yes I'm okay
Thank You
[Music]
Close Your Eyes please
okay
good morning
good morning come in please
open your eyes please
oh he has big ears
can you help me
sure I can
[Music]
how nice thank you
you're welcome
put on your hat please
great
foreign
how are you
[Music]
are you okay
I'm okay
the King has big ears
foreign
[Music]
Jack where are you
look here Mom oh no watch out okay
where's my box
it's on the desk
no it's not on the desk
look who's that
oh you have my box give it to me oh no
Mom I'm here watch out Jack
thank you
[Music]